designerscouch.org 2012-05-15

# About DesignersCouch

## Privacy Policy

DesignersCouch does not send Spam or sell email addresses.. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit our web sites and/or received any emails from DesignersCouch.

### 1\. Your personal information collected by DesignersCouch

In order to send you e-mail from DesignersCouch (if any), we need your e-mail address. To provide you with additional services, we may also request your name, geographical coordinates, and telephone number. DesignersCouch does not collect any other personal information that you do not expressly provide. DesignersCouch will not sell, rent or share your personal information, including your e-mail address, with any third parties for marketing purposes without your express permission. DesignersCouch may share your personal information for the purpose of delivering our e-mail to you or as required by law. Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, DesignersCouch may need to disclose personal information when required by law and when we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process that DesignersCouch receives. We may also collect demographic and other data, which may include Personally Identifiable Information, generally through surveys and forms, which you may or may not choose to participate in. If you place an order for goods or services through DesignersCouch, you may be required to enter your credit card number and information, as well as your shipping address and/or other contact information.

### 2\. Non-personal Information

We may also request non-personally identifiable information, such as buying preferences, or age, also known as demographic and profile data, though this information is optional. We may use this data to improve our website and/or customize your experience at our site, showing you content that we think you might be interested in, and displaying content according to your preferences. We may also share this information with others, such as advertisers interested in on our site, in aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any other person.

### 3\. Profile Page

If you choose to sign up for a free DesignersCouch account to enter participate in member only areas on the site, you may have a Profile page on the site, containing your username and some basic information related to demographics and your creative interests. You may also add additional optional information to your Profile. You may control what type of Profile information is shown to others through your Account Settings. Links to your Profile Page may be included on other DesignersCouch pages. PLEASE NOTE THAT, REGARDLESS OF WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION A MEMBER CHOOSES TO INCLUDE IN HIS OR HER PROFILE, OR WHAT PRIVACY PREFERENCES HE OR SHE CHOOSES, CERTAIN INFORMATION ABOUT EACH MEMBER WILL BE INCLUDED IN THAT MEMBER'S PUBLIC PROFILE AND MAY BE ACCESSIBLE TO ANYONE VISITING THAT PROFILE PAGE ON THE DESIGNERSCOUCH WEBSITE.

### 4\. Public Forum Reminder

This site often makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. Exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Although we value individual ideas and encourage free expression, DesignersCouch reserves the right to take necessary action to preserve the forum's integrity, such as removing any posting that is vulgar, off-topic, or inappropriate.

### 5\. Usage Information 

In addition to collecting personal and non-personal information, DesignersCouch may also collect non-personal, aggregated information about subscribers' use of our site. This information is not personally identifiable and will only be used to find out how subscribers use our service and site. For example, this information will tell us how much time users spend on our site, from which other sites subscribers came, and to what other sites subscribers go. The collection of this information allows us to, among other things, prepare for traffic load demands and to efficiently deliver relevant information. 

### 6\. Personally Identifiable Information Collected by DesignersCouch Business Partners. 

DesignersCouch may work with third-party advertising companies, sponsors and other companies with whom we do business ("Business Partners") to place advertising on our site and in email communications sent to our registered users regarding DesignersCouch services. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad, may be used to serve advertising to you on this site. DesignersCouch may correlate or match registered Users' information, including Personally Identifiable Information, with information held by our Business Partners to target ads or otherwise improve the effectiveness of our service. Our Business Partners may read or set cookies on your hard drive, use pixel tags, track which ads you have viewed, or collect other information about you. From time to time, DesignersCouch may also have special offers or promotions that are sponsored by a Business Partner. In order to participate in these offers, you may be required to follow a separate registration process. If you consent to receive information from a Business Partner, through an opt-in or opt-out process, DesignersCouch may pass your information to such Business Partner. DesignersCouch may also offer goods or services for purchase available by our Business Partners. If you purchase goods or services offered through DesignersCouch by a Business Partner, then you may be required to submit Personally Identifiable Information in order to complete the transaction and DesignersCouch may provide your Personally Identifiable Information to such Business Partner for that purpose. In some cases, we may enter into a promotional relationship with a Business Partner in which we prominently display their brand name or trademarks on pages that appear DesignersCouch pages. 

### 7\. Reviews and Access 

Upon your request, you can access a summary of the information we collect about you. You will have an opportunity to correct, update or modify this information. 

### 8\. Choice/Opt-Out 

If we ever send you information by e-mail concerning new products or services that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an e-mail address by which you may request no future notices. 

### 9\. Tracking 

Like most sites, DesignersCouch may make use of browser "cookies." Cookies are strings of text and numbers that can identify your computer to us when you visit our site. They allow us to see if you have logged in, check your status as a member, and facilitate access to your preferences. DesignersCouch will not use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to our site or services. DesignersCouch may also use transparent GIF images. We would use these images to track the e-mails that we send out. 

### 10\. IP Address 

When you visit our site, we log standard information such as your IP address, which is a number that can be used to identify your location and Internet Service Provider, along with the URL from which you came to our site and the URLs visited on our site. A URL is the full address of a Web site page, which may or may not contain some Personally Identifiable Information about the person who is viewing it. When we send messages to you or others, we may provide a URL link to the DesignersCouch site that contains an alphanumeric identifier, which allows us to identify the person to whom we sent the message so that we can personalize our content for that individual. 

### 11\. Third Party Cookies 

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. 

### 12\. Third Party 

Advertising Some of the ads appearing on our website may be delivered by one of our advertising partners. Information about your visit to their sites, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), may be used to serve ads to you. 

### 13\. Business Transactions 

In the event DesignersCouch. Goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. 

### 14\. Links to other sites 

As part of the services we provide, DesignersCouch may create links allowing you to access third party sites. DesignersCouch is not responsible for the content that appears on those sites and does not endorse these sites. Please consult those sites' individual privacy policies in order to determine how they treat user information. 

### 15\. Security 

All information described above is stored on restricted database servers. 

### 16\. Changes to this Policy 

DesignersCouch reserves the right to change this policy from time to time. If we do make changes, the revised Privacy Statement will be posted on this site. 13. Contact us If you have any questions about this policy or our site in general, please contact us at info [at] DesignersCouch [dot].
